advanstarhealthcare.com 2010-05-17

# About Us (Privacy Policy)

|  |   
---|---  
  
|  | 

Untitled Document

Advanstar Communications Inc.(together with its affiliated entities, "Advanstar") has created these privacy statements to demonstrate our commitment to full disclosure of the information collection and use practices applicable to this website. These privacy statements disclose what information we collect via this website and how we use it.

Corporate Privacy Policy   
Social Security Number Privacy Policy

Corporate Privacy Policy

 _Information Collection and Dissemination_ **  
General Principles**

  * In general, you may visit this website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.
  * As you browse our website, the site collects the IP address of your computer and clickstream data (information that site users generate as they move from page to page and click on items) and this data is aggregated with usage data from all site visitors.
  * Some portions of this website may require you to give us personally-identifiable information such as your name, job title, company, physical mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers (Personal Information) and, if applicable, financial information such as your credit card information (Financial Information), for, without limitation, (i) to register for attendance at certain Advanstar trade shows, conferences and events; (ii) to obtain access to certain online content and functionality; and (iii) to subscribe to our publications. If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communications may be collected as Personal Information.
  * If you elect to provide us Personal Information, we use it primarily to deliver the service you requested.
  * If you submit Financial Information, we use that information primarily to verify your credit and collect payments for your purchases, orders, registrations etc.

**Information Sharing**  
We share your Personal Information with Advanstar's affiliates and partners and third parties licensed to access your Personal Information by any of the foregoing. We rent lists compiled from the Personal Information (including e-mail addresses) gathered from this website.

Except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy, we will keep your Personal Information and your Financial Information private and will not share it with third parties. However, we reserve the right to release information about visitors, including Personal Information and Financial Information, when release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce our Terms of Service, or to protect the rights, property or safety of this website, the public or Advanstar.

On certain Advanstar websites, such as [www.modernmedicine.com](http://www.modernmedicine.com/), when you register for a Continuing Medical Education ("CME") or a Continuing Education ("CE") activity, we collect personally-identifiable information from you. This information is required to be collected by, and is shared with, the relevant accreditation bodies. Our Editorial and Customer Support Staff also have access to this information, including evaluation forms and participant information. This information is used in assessing educational needs and in planning marketing activities. We reserve the right to use this information as otherwise permitted in this Privacy Policy or in our Terms of Service Agreement.

**Aggregated information**  
We sometimes provide aggregated usage or tracking information collected from this website to third parties.

**Information on Children**  
As a business-to-business company, we do not knowingly collect information from children. On-line registration and web site usage is restricted to adults who are professionally engaged in the businesses we serve.

**Third Party and Affiliated Links:** Our websites contain links to external websites including suppliers, advertisers and affiliates. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the content of, or information gathered by, these other websites. We do not endorse any of these websites or the products or services associated with such websites merely because they are linked to our website.

**Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a string of data sent by a website to a user that is inserted in a file of the web browser of the user visiting the site. Advanstar uses temporary, session-specific cookies to ensure visits to its website are smooth and customized for the visitor. Such cookies allow us to provide a visitor's browser with information tailored to the visitor's preferences and needs. Advanstar also uses permanent or persistent cookies that remain on a visitor's computer after the visitor leaves an Advanstar website.

If you do not want your browser to accept cookies, you can turn off the cookie acceptance option in the browser's settings. However, disabling the cookie support function of the browser will prevent our website from functioning properly and you may not be able to use fully all of the site's features and information.

We use advertising companies to develop banner ads for our website. These ads may contain cookies. These companies collect cookies sent to your browser through the banner ads and we do not have control of, or access to, this data.

**Opt-out Option**  
Visitors to this website can decide whether they want to receive targeted promotional information from Advanstar. On the visitor registration pages, prospective visitors can choose to request Advanstar not to e-mail them advertising and promotional information. Should visitors accept promotional email from Advanstar, any email they receive will include instructions on how to be removed from Advanstar's promotional email list.

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
California's "Shine the Light" law, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83, permits our users who are residents of California to request and obtain from us, once per year, free of charge, information about the Personal Information and Financial Information, if any, that we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information includes a listing of the categories of personal information that was shared, and the names and addresses of the third parties with whom we shared the information.

If you are a California resident, and would like to make such a request, please submit your request, in writing, to:

Online Privacy Coordinator  
Advanstar Communications Inc.  
Legal Department  
131 West 1st Street  
Duluth, MN 55802

**Security and Encryption**  
This website takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your information. We use SSL encryption technology on the portions of our website that accept Financial Information and we use a secure server to encrypt Financial Information transmitted between your browser and our server. As a result, data you submit to our website, such as credit card and payment information, is transmitted securely over the Internet.

**Exceptions**  
Advanstar may buy or sell various assets. In the event that we sell some or all of our assets, or our site is acquired by another company, information about our visitors, including Personal Information and Financial Information, may be among the transferred assets.

Whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online - for example in chat rooms or on message boards - Advanstar has no ability or obligation to prevent third-party access to such information and Advanstar undertakes no responsibility to keep such information private.

**Notification of Changes**  
Advanstar reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this privacy policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the website.

**Your Acceptance of these Terms**  
By using our website, products or services, you signify your acceptance of the terms of the Advanstar Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the Advanstar Privacy Policy, please do not use the website, products and/or services and exit the site immediately. 

Social Security Number Privacy Policy 

**Statement of Purpose:**  
Advanstar Communications Inc. (together with its affiliated entities, “Advanstar”) has created this Social Security Number Privacy Protection Policy to demonstrate its commitment to maintaining the confidentiality of social security numbers Advanstar obtains in the ordinary course of its business activities from customers, creditors, contractors, vendors, employees and other individuals associated with Advanstar.

It is the policy of Advanstar to handle social security numbers obtained in the ordinary course of its business activities with a high degree of security and confidentiality. In general, Advanstar restricts access to information and documents containing social security numbers to Advanstar employees, agents and contractors who have a legitimate business reason to access such information and documents. Advanstar will ensure, to the extent practicable, that no individual associated with Advanstar obtains, stores, transfers, uses, discloses, or disposes of a social security number that Advanstar has obtained or possesses except in accordance with applicable law and this Privacy Policy. All Advanstar departments and business units having access to information, documents and records containing social security numbers will determine on an ongoing basis which personnel have a legitimate business reason to access those materials. No other Advanstar personnel will be authorized to access social security numbers maintained by Advanstar.

**Procedures:**

 _Protection of Social Security Numbers_   
In an effort to protect the privacy rights of individuals who provide their social security numbers to Advanstar, Advanstar will ensure, to the extent practicable, that: 

  * The confidentiality of social security numbers is maintained
  * Social security numbers are not unlawfully disclosed 
  * Records containing social security numbers are disposed of in a commercially reasonable manner (such as destroying, erasing or making unreadable social security numbers contained in data, computer files and documents) that minimizes the risk that social security numbers maintained by Advanstar will be obtained by unauthorized persons 
  * Social security numbers are not publicly displayed, used as the primary account number or identifier for an individual or printed on identification cards or badges 
  * Social security numbers are not used, transmitted or stored in documents, files, computer programs or databases that are not encrypted or secure 

_Authorized Use of Social Security Numbers_

This Privacy Policy does not prohibit the use of social security numbers obtained by Advanstar where the use is authorized or required by state or federal statute, rule, regulation, or court order or rule, or pursuant to legal or discovery process.

This Privacy Policy does not prohibit the collection or use of social security numbers belonging to customers, creditors, contractors, vendors, employees and other individuals associated with Advanstar for other legitimate business reasons, including, without limitation:

  * The conduct by Advanstar of pre-employment background, reference and related inquiries
  * For purposes of verifying employment candidates’ eligibility for employment by Advanstar
  * For employee tax reporting purposes, including new hire reporting and enrollment and participation in Advanstar benefit plans
  * For tax reporting purposes pertaining to customers, creditors, contractors, vendors and other individuals providing goods or services to Advanstar

Unauthorized Use or Disclosure  
Advanstar will take commercially reasonable measures to enforce this Privacy Policy and to correct and prevent the reoccurrence of any known violations. Non-compliance with this Privacy Policy may constitute a violation of federal and state law, and Advanstar will fully cooperate with all law enforcement and administrative agencies in the apprehension and prosecution of any person who knowingly obtains, uses or discloses social security numbers for any unlawful purpose. Willful violation of this Privacy Policy by Advanstar employees will result in disciplinary action up to and including discharge.

Notification of Changes   
Advanstar reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on this website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the website.   
  
---|---  
  
[Privacy Policy](http://web.advanstar.com/advanstar/v42/index.cvn?ID=10124) | [Terms of Use](http://web.advanstar.com/advanstar/v42/index.cvn?ID=10430) [Linking and RSS Policy](http://web.advanstar.com/advanstar/v42/index.cvn?ID=10429) | Site Map | © 2020 [Advanstar Communications, Inc.](http://web.advanstar.com/) All rights reserved.
